Hello and welcome to our English listening practice.
مرحبا بكم في تدريبنا على الاستماع للغة الإنجليزية.
How are you today?
كيف حالك اليوم؟
Today's lesson is very useful.
درس اليوم مفيد جدا.
We will learn important English words and phrases
سنتعلم كلمات وعبارات إنجليزية مهمة
for visiting a gas station.
لزيارة محطة وقود.
Imagine this, you are driving in another country.
تخيل هذا، أنت تقود في بلد آخر.
You need to stop at the gas station.
تحتاج للتوقف عند محطة الوقود.
Maybe you want to buy something from the shop
ربما تريد شراء شيء من المتجر
or you might need to ask the staff for help.
أو قد تحتاج إلى طلب المساعدة من الموظفين.
That's exactly what happened to me
هذا بالضبط ما حدث لي
when I traveled to another country alone.
عندما سافرت إلى بلد آخر وحدي.
But don't worry, I will make everything simple
لكن لا تقلق، سأجعل كل شيء بسيطا
and easy for you in this video.
وسهلة بالنسبة لك في هذا الفيديو.
I will speak slowly and clearly
سأتحدث ببطء ووضوح
so you can understand easily.
لذا يمكنك أن تفهم بسهولة.
If you want, you can repeat after me.
إذا أردت، يمكنك التكرار بعدي.
This will help improve your listening and speaking
هذا سيساعدك على تحسين الاستماع والتحدث
step by step.
خطوة بخطوة.
Are you ready?
هل أنت مستعد؟